

Ph.D STUDENT

Robotics and Computer Vision Lab., Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

□ (+82) 10-9509-3491 | 🗷 jjang9hsm@kaist.ac.kr | 🏕 soonminhwang.github.io | 🖸 soonminhwang | 🛅 smhwang

Summary_

(Willing to relocate abroad)

I am a Ph.D student advised by Prof. In So Kweon at KAIST, South Korea. I worked as a fulltime research intern in computer vision group at Qualcomm Research Austria. My research interest are robust visual perception technologies for autonomous driving in various conditions. I have broad interests about various computer vision algorithm for autonomous driving, e.g. object detection, segmentation, depth estimation, etc. I have been pursuing various computer vision algorithms to turn ultimate AI-powered sensors into reality.

Education _____

KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Daejeon, S.Korea

Mar. 2014 - Feb. 2019 (Expected)

Ph.D. STUDENT

- Dissertation: Visual sensor fusion for robust pedestrian detection
- Topic: Object detection, Deep learning, Sensor fusion
- Advisor: Prof. In So Kweon

KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Daejeon, S.Korea

M.S.

Feb. 2012 - Feb. 2014

- Thesis: A Hierarchical Classifier Model based on Deformable Part Models and Random Forest for Robust Pedestrian Detection
- Advisor: Prof. In So Kweon

Hanyang University Seoul, S. Korea

S. Mar. 2007 - Feb. 2012

• Recognize and Play a Music Score on Android Smartphone

Research Interests

Computer vision for self-driving cars

- Object detection (e.g. pedestrians, cars)
- Semantic segmentation / Depth estimation
- Image enhancement / 3D scene understanding

Deep learning for computer vision

- Dynamic neural network
- Adversarial machine learning for computer vision

Sensor fusion

- RGB camera + Thermal camera (Long wavelength IR)
- RGB camera + 3D LiDAR

Work experience_

Full-time Research Intern

Vienna, Austria

Jul. 2016 - Nov. 2016

Computer Vision Group, Qualcomm Research

· Lane marker detection using deep neural network

Hanyang Univ., Seoul, S.Korea

Nov. 2010 - Feb. 2011

MIXED REALITY LAB. (PROF. JONG-IL PARK)

• Development of view morphing system for relics

Projects.

Full-time Intern

Automatic Emergency Braking for Pedestrian Protection

Ministry of Trade, Industry and Energy of Korea (MOTIE)

• Accurate pedestrian detection using multiple sensor fusion

Jun. 2013 - PRESENT

Personal Plug and Play DigiCar (P3 DigiCar)

NATIONAL RESEARCH FOUNDATION OF KOREA Mar. 2012 - Feb. 2017

Robust pedestrian detection using monocular camera

DATMO: Detection and Tracking Moving Object using 3D LiDAR

LIG-Nex1 Co. Ltd, S.Korea *Apr.* 2015 - Nov. 2015

- On-road object detection and tracking (pedestrian, car) using 3D-LiDAR
- Camera & 3D LiDAR fusion

Monocular Vision based Natural Feature Extraction for Cognitive Model

MINISTRY OF KNOWLEDGE ECONOMY OF KOREA Sep. 2012 - Dec. 2013

• Porting developed natural feature algorithm to embedded system

Publications.

KAIST Multispectral Recognition Dataset in Day and Night

IEEE Transactions on Intelligent Transportation Systems (TITS)

Yukyung Choi, Namil Kim, Soonmin Hwang, Kibaek Park, Jae Shin Yoon, Kyunghwan An, In So Kweon

StairNet: Top-Down Semantic Aggregation for Accurate One Shot Detection

IEEE WINTER CONF. ON APPLICATIONS OF COMPUTER VISION (WACV)

Sanghyun Woo, **Soonmin Hwang**, In So Kweon

Multispectral Transfer Network: Unsupervised Depth Estimation for All-day Vision

THE THIRTY-SECOND AAAI CONFERENCE ON ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE (AAAI)

Namil Kim*, Yukyung Choi*, **Soonmin Hwang**, In So Kweon

Thermal Image Enhancement using Convolutional Neural Network

THE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF INTELLIGENT ROBOTS AND SYSTEMS (IROS)

Namil Kim*, Yukyung Choi*, **Soonmin Hwang***, In So Kweon

Fast Multiple Objects Detection and Tracking Fusing Color Camera and 3D LIDAR for Intelligent Vehicles

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON UBIQUITOUS ROBOTS AND AMBIENT INTELLIGENCE (URAI)

Soonmin Hwang*, Namil Kim*, Yukyung Choi, Seokju Lee, In So Kweon

Thermal-Infrared based Drivable Region Detection

IEEE INTELLIGENT VEHICLES SYMPOSIUM (IV)

Jae Shin Yoon, Kibaek Park, **Soonmin Hwang**, Namil Kim, Yukyung Choi, In So Kweon

Low-Cost Synchronization for Multispectral Cameras

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON UBIQUITOUS ROBOTS AND AMBIENT INTELLIGENCE (URAI)

Soonmin Hwang, Yukyung Choi, Namil Kim, Kibaek Park, Jae Shin Yoon, In So Kweon

Geometrical Calibration of Multispectral Calibration

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON UBIQUITOUS ROBOTS AND AMBIENT INTELLIGENCE (URAI)

Namil Kim, Yukyung Choi, **Soonmin Hwang**, Kibaek Park, Jae Shin Yoon, In So Kweon

ARTRIEVAL: Painting Retrieval Without Expert Knowledge

IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON IMAGE PROCESSING (ICIP)

Namil Kim, Yukyung Choi, **Soonmin Hwang**, In So Kweon

All-Day Visual Place Recognition: Benchmark Dataset and Baselines

IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON COMPUTER VISION AND PATTERN RECOGNITION WORKSHOPS (CVPRW-VPRICE)

Yukyung Choi, Namil Kim, Kibaek Park, **Soonmin Hwang**, Jae Shin Yoon, In So Kweon

Lake Tahoe, USA

Mar. 2018

2018

New Orleans, USA

Daejeon, S.Korea

Oct. 2016

Feb 2018

Xian, China

Aug. 2016

Gothenburg, Sweden

Jun. 2016

Goyang, S.Korea

Oct. 2015

Goyang, S.Korea

Oct. 2015

Québec, Canada

Sep. 2015

Boston, USA

Jun. 2015

Multispectral Pedestrian Detection: Benchmark Dataset and Baselines

Boston, USA

Jun. 2015

IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON COMPUTER VISION AND PATTERN RECOGNITION (CVPR)

Soonmin Hwang, Jaesik Park, Namil Kim, Yukyung Choi, In So Kweon

A Two Phase Approach for Pedestrian Detection

Singapore, Singapore

Nov. 2014

ASIAN CONFERENCE ON COMPUTER VISION WORKSHOPS (ACCV WORKSHOPS) **Soonmin Hwang**, Tae-hyun Oh, In So Kweon

Evaluation of Vocabulary Trees for Localization in Robot Applications

Gwangju, S.Korea

International Conference on Control, Automation and Systems (ICCAS)

Oct. 2013

Soonmin Hwang, Chaehoon Park, Yukyung Choi, Donggeun Yoo, In So Kweon

Honors & Awards

2018	Honorable mension	The 24th HumanTech Paper Award, Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd, (\$2,000, acceptance rate 6.5%)
2017	Gold prize	The 23th HumanTech Paper Award, Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd, (\$10,000, acceptance rate 0.7%)
2016	1st Place	NVidia Deep Learning Contest, NVidia Korea
2016	Bronze prize	Korea Invention Patent Exhibition (KINPEX)

Skills_

Languages Python, MATLAB, C/C++

Libraries PyTorch, Caffe, OpenCV, QT, PCL, MFC, and others